Finding Aid for Kenneth Ewart Boulding Papers 1880-1968
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Financial Records
  - Miscellaneous unprocessed (Box 45)
- Sound recordings
  - Growth Theory Seminar, February-May 1953; 8 audiotapes (Box 46)
    (transcripts in Box 39)
  - Communication and Information Theory Seminar, February-May 1954; 11 audiotapes (Box 46)
  - "The Image", August 1955; 24 audiotapes (Box 46)
  - Conflict Resolution Seminar, February-May 1956; 30 audiotapes (Box 46)
  - Agricultural Policy Speech at Iowa State University, Ames, circa 1963; 2 audiotapes (Box 46)
- Photographs
  The photographs series includes family photos, photos of Boulding's house in Ann Arbor, and photos of his peace activities; also photos of Elise Boulding and her activities.
  - Kenneth E. Boulding
    - Castles (Box 47)
    - With parents (Box 47)
    - Childhood and youth, 1910-1928 (Box 47)
    - Oxford and Liverpool, 1928-1932 (Box 47)
    - Chicago, etc., 1932-1934 (Box 47)
    - Edinburgh, etc., 1934-1937 (Box 47)
  - Kenneth E. and Elise Boulding
    - Hamilton, N.Y., etc., 1937-1941 (Box 47)
    - Ames, Iowa, etc., 1943-1949 (Box 47)
    - Ann Arbor, Mich., etc., 1949-1968 (Box 47)
    - Conferences, 1950-1967 (Box 47)
    - Peace activities (Box 47)
  - Biorn-Hansen family (Box 47)
  - Elizabeth Ann Rowe ("Bessie") Boulding (KEB's mother)
    - Photographs (Box 47)
    - Album, 1932 (Box 47)
  - William Boulding (KEB's grandfather) (Box 47)
  - William C. Boulding (KEB's father) (Box 47)
  - William C. and Elizabeth Boulding together (Box 47)
  - Boulding relatives (Box 47)
  - Chard, Somerset, England (Box 47)
  - Hardacre relatives (Box 47)
  - Ada Rowe (Box 47)
  - Flossie Rowe (Box 47)
  - George and Mary Rowe (Box 47)
  - Rowe relatives (Box 47)
  - Paintings and drawings (Box 47)
  - Memorial book, 1993 (Box 47)